(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Suspended in the void between stars,
a celestial music box twists open.
Within, seven points of light
await their moment to shine.
Now that the time has come, as they awaken,
their ethereal melody echoes out into the cosmos.
When those notes fall upon your ears,
where will they take you?
Listen well...
destiny beckons.
ララライ ララライ
La la lai, la la lai,
誰も知らない名も無い今を駆け抜けるの
running through this nameless present no one knows
あの三日月に手を伸ばして
Reach out your hand toward that crescent moon
ララライ ララライ
La la lai, la la lai,
君を知りたい声にならない臆病な朝を
wanting to know you in this silent, timid morning
たとえ何度迎えようとも
No matter how many times I face it
臍の緒パチンと切られたその時
The moment the umbilical cord was snipped
世界と逸れてしまったみたいだ
It felt as if I’d strayed away from the world
眼に映る景色が 悲しく笑うなら
If the scenery reflected in your eyes is sad
恐れず瞼を閉じてごらん
Don't be afraid, try closing your eyelids
さあ皆さまこちらへ
Now, everyone, come this way,
どうぞ鼓動の鳴る方へ さあ
please, head towards where the heartbeat sounds
かかと打ち鳴らせ
Come, click your heels,
どうぞ心の躍る方へ さあ
please, head towards where your heart dances
蜃気楼に飛び乗って
Jump onto the mirage,
さかしまな世界乗りこなして
and master this upside-down world
ララライ ララライ 止まない愛を知りたい願う御呪い
La la lai, la la lai, an incantation to know love
時を超えて朝から夜まで
Transcending time, from morning until night
ララライ ララライ
La la lai, la la lai,
君を知りたい何一つ見逃さぬように
wanting to know you, so as not to miss a thing
時は誰も待ってくれないの
Time waits for no one
さあ残酷な運命が
Come, even if a cruel fate
抗えぬ宿命が
and an irresistible destiny
考える間もなく 押し寄せ去るなら
surge forward before you can even think,
さあ前が見えなくたって
come, even if you can't see what's ahead,
君を信じてみたいの
I want to try believing in you
恐れずに一歩踏み出したら
If you take a step forward without fear,
さあ皆さまこちらへ
now, everyone, come this way,
どうぞ鼓動の鳴る方へ さあ
please, head towards where the heartbeat sounds
かかと打ち鳴らせ
Come, click your heels,
どうぞ心の躍る方へ さあ
please, head towards where your heart dances
さあ皆さまこちらへ
Now, everyone, come this way,
どうぞ鼓動の鳴る方へ さあ
please, head towards where the heartbeat sounds
かかと打ち鳴らせ
Come, click your heels,
どうぞ心の躍る方へ さあ
please, head towards where your heart dances
空飛ぶ鯨に飛び乗って
Jump onto the flying whale,
さかしまな世界踊り尽くせ
dance your fill in this upside-down world
ララライ ララライ
La la lai, la la lai,
誰も知らない名も無い今を駆け抜けるの
running through this nameless present no one knows
あの三日月に手を伸ばして
Reach out your hand toward that crescent moon
ララライ ララライ
La la lai, la la lai,
君を知りたい声にならない臆病な朝を
wanting to know you in this silent, timid morning
例え何度...
No matter how many times...
...迎えようとも
...I face it.
夢ならば醒めないで
If it's a dream, don't wake me up.
現実なんてもう身も蓋もないから
Because reality is already so cold and blunt.
時は誰も待ってくれないの
Time waits for no one.
無敵の笑顔で荒らすメディア
An invincible smile, trashing the media.
知りたいその秘密ミステリアス
Want to know her secret, so mysterious.
抜けてるとこさえ彼女のエリア
Even her clumsy side is her territory.
完璧で嘘つきな君は
You, perfect and a liar...
天才的なアイドル様
Are a genius-like idol.
アイドル
Lyrics, Music: Ayase
Idol
今日何食べた？
What did you eat today?
好きな本は？
What's your favorite book?
遊びに行くならどこに行くの？
If you were to go out, where would you go?
何も食べてない
I haven't eaten anything.
それは内緒
That's a secret.
何を聞かれても
No matter what you ask,
のらりくらり
she dodges it so smoothly.
淡々と だけど燦々と
Detached, yet so radiantly,
見えそうで見えない秘密は蜜の味
a secret just out of reach tastes like honey.
あれもないないない
Not that, no, no, no.
これもないないない
Not this, no, no, no.
好きなタイプは？ 相手は？ さあ答えて
What's your type? Who's the one? Come on, tell us.
「誰かを好きになることなんて私分からなくてさ」
"I don't really know what it's like to fall in love."
嘘か本当か知り得ない
Whether it's a lie or the truth, I'll never know.
そんな言葉にまたひとり落ちる
Another person falls for those words again.
また好きにさせる
Making them love you again.
誰もが目を奪われていく
Everyone is captivated by you,
君は完璧で究極のアイドル
the perfect and ultimate idol.
金輪際現れない
Never to appear again,
一番星の生まれ変わり
the reincarnation of the brightest star.
その笑顔で愛してるで
With that smile and those "I love yous,"
誰も彼も虜にしていく
you captivate everyone and anyone.
その瞳が その言葉が
Those eyes, those words...
嘘でもそれは完全なアイ
even if they're lies, it's a complete love.
はいはいあの子は特別です
Yes, yes, that girl is special.
我々は鼻からおまけです
We're just extras from the start.
お星様の引き立て役Bです
Sidekick B to make the star shine brighter.
全てがあの子のお陰なわけない
There's no way everything is thanks to her.
洒落臭い
How annoying.
妬み嫉妬なんてない わけがない
Envy and jealousy? Of course I feel them.
これはネタじゃない
This isn't a joke,
からこそ許せない
and that's why I can't forgive it.
完璧じゃない君じゃ許せない
I can't forgive you for not being perfect.
自分を許せない
I can't forgive myself.
誰よりも強い君以外認めない
I won't accept anyone but you, the strongest.
誰もが信じ崇めてる
Everyone believes and worships her,
まさに最強で無敵のアイドル
the truly strongest and invincible idol.
弱点なんて見当たらない
Not a single weakness to be found,
一番星を宿している
harboring the brightest star within.
弱いとこなんて見せちゃダメダメ
You must never, ever show your weak side.
知りたくないとこは見せずに
Without showing the parts they don't want to see,
唯一無二じゃなくちゃイヤイヤ
you must be one of a kind, no, no!
それこそ本物のアイ
That is what true love is.
得意の笑顔で沸かすメディア
Firing up the media with her signature smile,
隠しきるこの秘密だけは
this secret is the only thing she'll keep hidden.
愛してるって嘘で積むキャリア
Building a career on the lie of "I love you,"
これこそ私なりの愛だ
this is my own way of showing love.
流れる汗も綺麗なアクア
The flowing sweat is a beautiful aqua,
ルビーを隠したこの瞼
the eyelids that hide the rubies.
歌い踊り舞う私はマリア
Singing and dancing, I am Maria.
そう嘘はとびきりの愛だ
Yes, lies are the ultimate form of love.
誰かに愛されたことも
Having never been loved by anyone,
誰かのこと愛したことも
and having never loved anyone else...
ないそんな私の嘘が
I hope that my lie...
いつか本当になること信じてる
...will one day become the truth.
いつかきっと全部手に入れる
One day, I'll surely have it all.
私はそう欲張りなアイドル
I am a greedy idol after all.
等身大でみんなのこと
Because I want to love everyone...
ちゃんと愛したいから
...just as I am,
今日も嘘をつくの
I tell lies again today.
この言葉がいつか本当になる日を願って
Hoping for the day these words come true.
それでもまだ君と君にだけは言えずにいたけれど
Even so, I still haven't been able to tell you and only you, but...
やっと言えた
I finally said it.
これは絶対嘘じゃない
This is definitely not a lie.
愛してる
I love you.
哀しい欲望に
To the sorrowful desires
手を伸ばし続けて
Continuing to reach out my hand
夢を見る
I dream
何もかも いっそ
Everything, might as well
嘘に塗れた眼の中に
Inside eyes covered in lies
真実が
The truth is
隠れたまま
Remaining hidden
希望の淵に呑まれて
Swallowed by the abyss of hope
沈んでしまった
And sunk away
本当の答えを
The true answer...
探し続けながら
...while continuing to search
何百回でも
No matter how many hundreds of times
遮るモノに
Against the things that block the way
翳してみせる
I'll hold it up
僕の願い
My wish
必ず
Surely
君に伝える 日まで
Until the day I convey it to you
正しさは
As for correctness
譲れないから
Since I cannot yield
進み続けてゆくの
I will keep moving forward
何度でも
No matter how many times
彷徨いながら
While wandering
目指して
Aiming for
いつか黎明の元へ
Someday, to the source of dawn
帰る時まで
Until the time to return
痛む泥濘の中で
Inside the painful mire
祈りを描くよ
I'll draw a prayer
心配ないと言い
Telling myself there's no need to worry
聞かせながら今
While making myself listen, right now
歩き出すの
I start walking
冷めた約束の
Of the cooled promise
絵を繋ぎ合わせた
Joining the pictures together
道を往く
I walk the path
重ね合う
Overlapping
夢に息吐く場所などないと
That there is no place to breathe in dreams
どこかで
Somewhere
怯えながら
While being afraid
鼓動は
The heartbeat
光求めて
Seeking light
不自由な軌道を選んだ
Selected an unfree orbit
それが
That is...
今を苦しめても
...even if it torments the present
もう一回はない！
There is no second time!
愚かなほどに 望んでしまう
Desiring to a foolish extent
光る世界
A shining world
抱えて 押し潰されかけても
Even if I'm crushed while holding it
後悔なら
If it's regret
呆れるほどに 繰り返してきたけれど
I've repeated it to an amazing extent, but...
真実を
The truth...
もう失いたくないから
...since I don't want to lose it anymore
歪な運命の中に 囚われている
Imprisoned within a distorted fate
荒ぶ人生を共に
Together through a wild life
あなたと歩くよ
I will walk with you
涙の果ては
The end of tears
此処ではないと思おう
Let's think it's not here
夜を渡ってゆく
Crossing through the night
あの日僕らが出会った時に見た大きな夢は、
The big dream we saw when we met that day,
二人のレンズにはそれぞれ別の景色だった。
was a different scenery in each of our lenses.
それでも何故か二人には美しく見えて心が熱くなって
Even so, for some reason it looked beautiful to both of us, and my heart raced
どうしようもなく叫びたくなったのは今でも覚えてる。
and I still remember how I wanted to scream uncontrollably.
主題はきっとそれだけで過不足ないから、
Because the theme itself is surely sufficient,
美しくという鍵を荒らして永遠に追いかけながら、
While chasing forever, roughing up the key called "beauty",
何も間違いじゃない、声を震わせ歌いながら、
Nothing is a mistake, while singing with a trembling voice,
君の手を引く、今生き抜くことが出来たなら。
Pulling your hand, if we could survive now.
深い
Deep
旅をしよう
Let's take a journey
その先は ほとほとが罪かもしれないし、
The path ahead may be mostly sin,
その先は ほとほとが光ばかりかもしれないけれど
The path ahead may be nothing but light, but...
永い
Long
地図を記そう
Let's mark the map
分かっていたはずだ、逃げることなんてできなかったから、
We should have known, because we couldn't run away,
最後の一句を、最後の歌を...
The last phrase, the last song...
青い
Blue
星を巡る
Travel the star
谷々に響くまで
Until it echoes through the valleys
決して止まってはいけないのだった、きっと誰も知っていた...
We weren't supposed to ever stop, surely everyone knew...
苦しみさえ 引き連れて
Taking even the suffering with us
深層へ
To the depths
何百回でも
No matter how many hundreds of times
遮るモノに 翳してみせる
I'll hold it up against the things that block the way
僕の願い
My wish
必ず 君に伝える 日まで
Until the day I surely convey it to you
正しさは 譲れないから
Since I cannot yield correctness
進み続けてゆくの
I will keep moving forward
何度でも 彷徨いながら
No matter how many times, while wandering
目指して
Aiming for
いつか黎明の元へ 帰る時まで
Until the time to return someday to the source of dawn
痛む泥濘の中で 祈りを描くよ
I'll draw a prayer inside the painful mire
心配ないと言い聞かせながら今
Telling myself there's no need to worry, right now
歩き出すの
I start walking
たった一つの
A single...
朝焼けを
...dawn
手に入れるの
I'll take it in my hand
花になって
Lyrics: 長屋晴子 Music: 穴見真吾
Become a Flower
Lyrics: Haruko Nagaya Music: Shingo Anami
陰にそっと隠れようがいいんじゃない？
Why not just hide away in the shadows?
つぼみのような花だっていいんじゃない？
Why not be a flower that's still a bud?
秘密にして守るのがいいんじゃない？
Why not keep it a secret and protect it?
誰にも邪魔されず可憐に咲いて
Blooming beautifully without anyone in your way
甘い苦いにハマんない その判断がくだんない
Not caught up in sweet or bitter, that judgment is pointless
気に病んで下を向かないでいて
Don't let it get to you and look down
愛になっちゃいない 無駄に飾らない
It hasn't become love, so don't decorate it needlessly
綺麗にされた花瓶も 肥やしも何もいらない
I don't need a pretty vase, or fertilizer, or anything
その姿が美しい
Your appearance just as it is, is beautiful
花になって
Become a flower
ほらニヒルに笑って
Come on, give a nihilistic smile
その真顔に
At that serious face
ゾクゾクして目が離せない
I get a thrill and can't look away
味見して
Take a taste
君の毒は私の薬って
Saying your poison is my medicine
包んであげるから
Because I'll wrap it all up
笑って
Smile
逢いたい 逢いたい その笑顔に 逢いたい 逢いたい
I want to see, I want to see your smile, I want to see, I want to see
って言えば笑ってくれるかな
If I say that, I wonder if you'll smile?
陰から支えるくらいがいいんじゃない？
Isn't it enough to just support you from the shadows?
欲を言えばこの手で咲かせてみたい
If I were to be greedy, I'd want to make you bloom with these hands
病のように心を喰らう花
A flower that devours the heart like a disease
枯らしたくないのさ
I don't want you to wither
光が届かずとも
Even if the light doesn't reach
水をあげ続けるから
I'll keep giving you water
いい加減に気付いて 君は素敵って
Please just realize that you're wonderful
自惚れてもっとね大事に
Be conceited and take better care of yourself
無自覚なまま愛を蓄えて
Accumulating love while being unaware of it
綺麗にされた花瓶も 肥やしも何もいらない
I don't need a pretty vase, or fertilizer, or anything
その姿で咲き誇れ
Bloom in full glory, just as you are
花になって
Become a flower
ほらニヒルに笑って
Come on, give a nihilistic smile
その真顔に
At that serious face
ゾクゾクして目が離せない
I get a thrill and can't look away
味見して
Take a taste
君の毒は私の薬って
Saying your poison is my medicine
包んであげるから
Because I'll wrap it all up
楽にして
Put your mind at ease
君の闇は私の光って
Saying your darkness is my light
愛してあげるから
Because I'll love you
笑って
Smile
Ubiquitous dB
Lyrics: hotaru Music: やしきん
Lyrics: hotaru Music: Yashikin
曖昧なボリュームじゃまだ足りないなんて
An ambiguous volume is still not enough
I'm for you...
世界は透明な
The world is transparent
境界線はもう
The boundaries are already
どこにもない
Nowhere to be found
感情の波を 散々伝えるよ
I'll convey the waves of emotion over and over
答えてよ
Please answer me
七色しよう
Let's make it rainbow-colored
エモーショナルグラフィー
Emotionalgraphy
君に届いているかな
I wonder if it's reaching you
もう研ぎ澄ませて
Already sharpened
波状的信号 コミュニケートできるかな
Wave-like signals, I wonder if we can communicate
見つけてみて
Try to find it
声の中の
Inside the voice
ピュアなとこ
The pure part
鳴らせハイファイな想いと
Let the high-fidelity feelings ring out
次元を超え胸打つメロディ
A melody that crosses dimensions and strikes the heart
そしてリアルな秘密教えよう
And let me tell you a real secret
この歌は永遠に生きていくよ
This song will live on forever
だから会いたいなんてナンセンス
So saying "I want to meet" is nonsense
指先刺すよ 君のメモリに
I'll pierce your memory with my fingertips
ほら
Look
君が私を呼ぶ
You're calling me
ほら
Look
耳澄まして
Listen closely
限界掲示の現状だから
Because it's the current state of showing limits
提示して差し上げて
Present it and offer it
一人きりだなんて壁はもう
The wall of being all alone is already
通用しない
No longer effective
一緒にいよう それが歌だから
Let's be together, because that's what a song is
託してよ
Entrust it to me
共鳴いきよう エモーションレスキュー
Let's live in resonance, Emotion Rescue
君にちゃんと見えるかな
I wonder if you can see it clearly
もっと手を振って
Wave your hands more
感情的感情 大ダイレクト
Emotional feelings, big and direct
見つけた
I found it
点滅してる それが君の
It's blinking, that's your
ピュアなとこ
Pure part
響けアッパーなリズムで
Resonate with an upbeat rhythm
強制的上げ手くハートビート
A heartbeat that's forced to rise
ごめん 手の先 聞いてほしいんだ
Sorry, I want you to listen to the tips of my hands
君のためだけに歌うから
Because I'm singing just for you
なぜかちょっと泣けちゃって
For some reason, I cried a little
君が笑ってくれたせいだけど
It's because you smiled for me
そうか
I see
通じ合える暖かさは
The warmth of understanding each other
初めてかな
Is it the first time?
ここはどこでしょう
Where is this?
私は誰でしょう
Who am I?
声を頼りに探してよ
Rely on the voice and search for me
心で歌うよ
I'll sing with my heart
心に届いてほしいよ
I want it to reach your heart
夢もリアルも
Both dreams and reality
本当だよ
Are true
鳴らせハイファイな想いと
Let the high-fidelity feelings ring out
次元を超え胸打つメロディ
A melody that crosses dimensions and strikes the heart
そしてリアルな秘密教えよう
And let me tell you a real secret
この歌は永遠に生きていくよ
This song will live on forever
だから会いたいなんてナンセンス
So saying "I want to meet" is nonsense
指先刺すよ 君のメモリに
I'll pierce your memory with my fingertips
ほら
Look
君が私を呼ぶ
You're calling me
ほら
Look
耳澄まして
Listen closely
いつも
Always
そばにいるよ
I'll be by your side
デシベルを上げて
Raising the decibels
優しい言葉を
Kind words...
貴方がくれた
...that you gave me.
寂しい時には
When I am lonely...
抱きしめてくれて
...you hold me tight.
Hello...
哀しいこともあったけど
There were sad times too
浅い春の喜びも
The joys of early spring
二人で分け合った
We shared them together
時が終わる前に
Before time ends
遠い独り
Far away, alone
残したい言葉を
The words I want to leave
探した
I searched for
「ありがとう」とただ繰り返した
I just repeated "Thank you" over and over
それだけが貴方の胸に
I hope that alone, to your heart
届けばいい
Will reach
心よどうか遠く
Please, my heart, reach far
空を駆けて
Fly through the sky
微笑みを貴方に伝えて
And bring my smile to you
消えて行く春の
Of the fading spring
名残のような
Like a lingering memory
温もりだけをその胸に
Keep just that warmth in your heart
そっと
Gently
残して行けたら
If I could leave it behind
smile for you...
ユグドラシル
Yggdrasil
世界の果ての
At the end of the world
大いなる木の麓より
From the foot of the Great Tree
永遠の果てへ
To the end of eternity
旅立つは歌声
The singing voice sets off
季節は巡りて
As the seasons turn
種はいつか芽吹いて
The seeds will one day sprout
見守り 見送りに
Watching over, seeing them off
花は実を残す
The flowers leave behind fruit
時の水面に消えて行く名も
Even names that fade on the surface of time
ただ一人覚えていよう
I alone will remember them
ここに誰かがいた証
Proof that someone was here
ここには君が確かにいたと
That you were certainly here
古の調べは
The ancient melody
明日も歌うだろう
Will probably sing tomorrow too
海原を行く
Going across the ocean
風を追い解くのバラード
A ballad that follows and unravels the wind
荒野を歩む
Walking the wilderness
誇り高き騎士の音
The sound of a proud knight
悪戯を追って落ちたおさなびは
The childhood spark that fell chasing a prank
世界の秘め事記されている
The secrets of the world are recorded
過去も未来も幻だから
Because both past and future are illusions
いつでも君に会いに行けるよ
I can go to see you anytime
季節は巡りて
The seasons turn
友は先に行き
Friends go on ahead
今、独り、見送り
Now, alone, seeing them off
いつも残されて
Always being left behind
君の屍も土に返そう
Let's return your remains to the earth too
いつか世界樹の下で会おう
Let's meet under the world tree someday
その時まではさよならだから
Because until then, it's goodbye
一粒の涙を
A single teardrop
時の海原に消えてゆくの
Disappearing into the ocean of time
ただ一人だけを覚えていよう
I'll remember just one person
ここには君が確かにいたと
That you were certainly here
古の調べは
The ancient melody
明日も歌うだろう
Will probably sing tomorrow too
世界の果ての
At the end of the world
大いなる樹を
The great tree
称えて歌おう
Let's sing in its praise
花の唄
Song of Flowers
その日々は夢のように
Those days, like a dream
臆病な微笑みと
With a timid smile
やさしい爪を残して行った
And leaving gentle claws behind
退屈な花びらのように
Like boring petals
苦しみを忘れて
Forgetting the pain
貴方の背中でそっと
Softly on your back
泣いて笑った
I cried and laughed
帰らぬ日々を思うような
As if thinking of days that won't return
奇妙な愛しさに満ちた
Filled with a strange affection
箱庭の中で
Inside the miniature garden
息をひそめ
Holding my breath
季節が行くことを忘れ
Forgetting that the seasons pass
静かな水底のような
Like a quiet bottom of the water
時間にいた
I was in that time
冷たい花びら夜に散り咲く
Cold petals scatter and bloom in the night
まるで白い雪のようだね切なく
Just like white snow, isn't it, so painfully
貴方の上に降った悲しみを全て
All the sadness that fell upon you
払い除けてあげたいだけ
I just want to brush it all away
貴方のこと傷つけるもの
The things that hurt you
傷つけるもの全て 私はきっと許すことは出来ない
All those that hurt, I'm sure I won't be able to forgive.
優しい日々
Gentle days,
涙が出るほど帰りたい
I want to return so much that I could cry.
貴方と二人で見上げた
We looked up together,
花びらが散った
And the flower petals scattered.
月が雲に隠れて
The moon hid behind the clouds,
貴方は道を失くして
And you lost your way,
泣き出しそうな
Looking like you'd start to cry,
目をしてた
With those eyes.
ぎざぎざなこころだって
Even a jagged heart,
ふたつ合わせてみれば
If you put two together,
優しいものがきっと
I'm sure something gentle
生まれてくるわ
Will be born.
私を傷つけるものを
The things that hurt me,
貴方は許さないでくれた
You didn't forgive.
それだけでいいの
That's enough for me.
戯れに伸ばされた
Stretched out playfully,
貴方の手にしがみ付いた
I clung to your hand.
諦めていた世界に
In the world I'd given up on,
やがて温かな
Eventually, a warm
灯がともる
Light will be lit.
冷たい花びら夜を切り裂く
Cold petals tear through the night.
私が摘んだ光をみんな束ねて
I gather all the light I've plucked,
貴方の上に全部
And all over you,
よろこびのように撒き散らしてあげたいだけ
I just want to scatter it like joy.
わるいことをしたらきっと
If I did something bad, I'm sure
貴方が怒ってくれると約束したよね
You promised that you'd get angry at me.
だからきっともう一度
So I'm sure you'll,
私を見つけてくれるよね
Find me once again.
寂しいところにもういなくていいね
It's okay to not be in a lonely place anymore.
一人で見上げた
I looked up alone,
花びらが散った
And the flower petals scattered.
バグ
Bug
Lyrics, Music: かいりきベア
Lyrics, Music: Kairiki Bear
迷子迷子 真っ只中さ パッパッパラ パラノイア
Lost, lost, right in the middle of it. Pa-pa-pa-ra, paranoia.
ギコギコ 迷子 心連ね パッパッパラ パラノイア
Creak, creak, lost, hearts linked. Pa-pa-pa-ra, paranoia.
絶え絶え 絶えた 絡まった パッパッパラ パラノイア
Faintly, faded, entangled. Pa-pa-pa-ra, paranoia.
パッパパラッパ パッパラ
Pa-pa-para-ppa Pa-ppara
逃げ道の果て
At the end of the escape route
まぜ 虚 虚 感情 パッパラの嫌
Mix, void, void feelings, Pa-ppara-no-iya
踊れ どえらい 下手っ端 ぐるぐる
Dance, incredibly clumsy, round and round
バグ バグ 詰め 詰め やっぱ やっぱの馬鹿
Bug bug, stuff stuff, after all, after all a fool
沈め ぜんぜん 嫌 嫌 嫌
Sink, not at all, no no no
パッパパラッパ パッバラバグ
Pa-pa-para-ppa Pa-ppara bug
まじ 虚 虚 嫌 嫌
Mix, void, void, no no
パッパパラッパ パッバラバグ
Pa-pa-para-ppa Pa-ppara bug
答え 出せ 出せ 嫌 嫌 嫌
Give the answer, give it, no no no
嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌
No no no no no no
ぐるぐる
Round and round
バッカバカッパ 待って 無理 ぐるぐる
Stupid, wait, impossible, round and round
背負って 回れ
Carry it and spin
バッカバカッパ やっぱ 無理 ぐるぐる
Stupid, after all impossible, round and round
愛の 鎖
Chain of love
エンドレス 病み
Endless sickness
だっこ だっこ 言いたい子
The child who wants to be held
パッパパラッパ パッバラバグ
Pa-pa-para-ppa Pa-ppara bug
一歩 一歩 頑張れぬ
One step, one step, can't work hard
反目 ミスレス
The mistress of antagonism
パッパパラッパ パッバラバグ
Pa-pa-para-ppa Pa-ppara bug
ランランバグ ランパムバグ
Ran-ran bug, Ran-pam bug
ロンロンバグ 反故のバグ
Ron-ron bug, bug of betrayal
パッパパラッパ パッパラ パッパラの嫌
Pa-pa-para-ppa Pa-ppara Pa-ppara-no-iya
パッパラの嫌
Pa-ppara-no-iya
パッパラの嫌 嫌 嫌
Pa-ppara-no-iya iya iya
さあ 混じる 虚 虚 感情 パッパラの嫌
Come, mix, void, void feelings, Pa-ppara-no-iya
右に 左に 行方 も ぐるぐる
Right to left, even the destination is round and round
いざ 限界 の 来ちゃって 滅茶苦茶
Now the limit has come, it's a mess
病み 迷え 嫌 嫌 嫌
Be sick and lost, no no no
嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌
No no no no no
さあ 混じる 虚 虚 感情 パッパラの嫌
Come, mix, void, void feelings, Pa-ppara-no-iya
踊れ どえらい 下手っ端 ぐるぐる
Dance, incredibly clumsy, round and round
混じる 虚 虚 嫌 嫌 滅茶苦茶
Mix, void, void, no no, a mess
ここは どこ 嫌 嫌 嫌
Where is this, no no no
パッパパラッパ パッバラバグ
Pa-pa-para-ppa Pa-ppara bug
絶叫 虚 虚 感情 嫌 嫌 嫌
Scream, void, void feelings, no no no
パッパパラッパ パッバラバグ
Pa-pa-para-ppa Pa-ppara bug
狂い 震え 嫌 嫌 嫌
Go crazy and tremble, no no no
嫌 嫌 嫌
No no no
嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌
No no no no no no no no
'ODDS & ENDS'
Lyrics, Music: ryo(supercell)
いつだって君は嗤われ者だ
Always, you've been a laughingstock.
やることなすことツイてなくて
Nothing you do ever goes right.
挙句に雨に降られ
And to top it off, you're caught in the rain.
お気に入りの傘は風で飛んでって
Your favorite umbrella blown away by the wind.
そこのノラはご苦労様と
That stray over there, as if saying "nice job"...
足をふんづけてった
...stepped right on your foot.
いつもどおり君は嫌われ者だ
As usual, you're the outcast.
何にもせずとも遠ざけられて
Ostracized even when you do nothing.
努力をしてみるけど
Though you try your best,
その理由なんてなんとなくで
the reason for it is just "because".
君は途方に暮れて悲しんでた
You were at a loss and in despair.
「なら あたしの声を使えばいいよ
“Well then, you can use my voice instead.”
人によっては理解不能で
“To some, it's incomprehensible,”
なんて耳障り、ひどい声だって
“and they'll say it's jarring and awful.”
言われるけど」
“But regardless...”
「きっと君の力になれる
“I'm sure I can be your strength.”
だからあたしを歌わせてみて
“So let me sing for you.”
そう君の、君だけの言葉でさ」
“With your words—words that belong only to you.”
綴って 連ねて
Write them out, string them together,
あたしがその思想を叫ぶから
and I will scream those thoughts for you.
描いて 理想を
Paint your ideals,
その想いは誰にも触れさせない
and I won't let anyone touch those feelings.
ガラクタの声はそして響く
The voice of junk then resounds,
ありのままを不器用に繋いで
linking reality together clumsily...
目一杯に
...with everything it's got!
声を上げる
...raising my voice.
いつからか君は人気者だ
Since some point, you've become popular.
たくさんの人にもてはやされ
Being celebrated by many people,
あたしも鼻が高い
and I feel proud too.
でもいつからか君は変わった
But at some point, you changed.
冷たくなって だけど寂しそうだった
Becoming cold, yet you looked lonely.
もう機械の声なんてたくさんだ
I've had enough of "machine voices."
僕は僕自身なんだよって
Saying, "I am myself."
ついに君は抑えきれなくなって
Finally, you couldn't hold it back anymore,
あたしを嫌った
and you hated me.
君の後ろで誰かが言う
Behind your back, someone says,
虎の威を借るキツネの群れに
to the pack of foxes borrowing the tiger's authority...
ねぇ君は
Hey, you...
一人で泣いてたんだね
You were crying all alone, weren't you?
聴こえる？
Can you hear it?
この声
This voice.
あたしがその誹謗を
I will take those slanders...
かき消すから
...and drown them out.
わかってる 本当は
I know. The truth is...
君が誰より優しいってことを
...that you are kinder than anyone else.
ガラクタの声はそして歌った
And then the junk voice sang,
他の誰でもない君のために
not for anyone else, but for you.
軋んでいく
Creaking along,
限界を超えて
beyond the limits.
二人はどんなにたくさんの言葉を思いついたことだろう
I wonder how many words the two of us came up with.
だけど今は何ひとつ思いつかなくて
But now I can't think of a single thing,
だけど何もかもわかった
yet I understood everything.
「そうか、きっとこれは夢だ。」
"I see, this must be a dream."
永遠に覚めない
A dream I'll never wake up from,
君と会えた、そんな夢
the dream of meeting you.
ガラクタは幸せそうな表情をしたまま
With the junk still wearing a happy expression,
どれだけ呼んでももう動かない
no matter how much you call, it no longer moves.
望んだはずの結末に
At the ending you must have wanted,
君は泣き叫ぶ
you cry out.
「嘘だろ、嘘だろ」って
Crying out, "It's a lie, right? It's a lie!"
そう泣き叫ぶ
Cry out just like that.
「僕は
"I am...
無力だ。ガラクタ
...powerless. Even one piece...
一つだって救えやしない」
...of junk, I cannot save."
想いは 涙に
Thoughts... in tears,
ぽつりぽつりと
drip by drip,
その頬を濡らす
wetting those cheeks.
その時 世界は
In that moment, the world...
途端にその色を
...suddenly its colors...
大きく変える
...greatly changed.
悲しみ 喜び
Sadness, joy,
全てを一人と
everything, with one person...
ひとつが知った
...and one piece, became known.
言葉は歌になりこの世界を
Words become a song and travel the world...
再び駆け巡る君のために
...once more, for you.
その声に意志を宿して
Imbuing that voice with will,
今 想いが響く
now, thoughts resonate.
TEMARI
Lyrics: LUMINA
Music, Arrangement: seibin
さあ 散らばってしまった話を
Now, a story that has scattered...
空に手を伸ばし始める
I begin to reach my hands towards the sky.
下を通り過ぎる曲がった線に
To the curved lines passing below,
縛られた足をくすぐるの
tickling my bound feet.
嗚呼 落ちて汚れた意識を
Ah, the consciousness that fell and became stained,
名前と呪術にかけて
casting names and sorcery.
空っぽだった体の
Of the body that was empty,
夢見ていたまぶたが開く
the eyelids that were dreaming open.
心の奥からうごめく記憶...
Memories wriggling from deep within the heart...
ゆらゆら
Swaying...
混じった呪いと祝福が
The mixed curse and blessing...
目の前を
...before my eyes...
知ってるの？
Do you know?
始まりと終わりに 向かって
Towards the beginning and the end...
果てに、帰ってくるのは
...what comes back in the end is...
パパの呼び声だけ
...only Papa's calling voice.
嗚呼、パパ、
Ah, Papa...
そこに居たら教えて欲しいの
If you are there, I want you to tell me...
私が歩くこの道は
...this path that I walk...
どんな色だろう
...what color will it be?
さあ、この調べの旋律を
Now, this melody of investigation...
空に手を伸ばし始める
...start reaching out to the sky...
散らばった 遠くの地のいろ
The scattered colors of distant lands...
愛を渇望して 泣き叫んでる
...crying out, thirsting for love.
始まりと終わりに 向かって
Towards the beginning and the end...
果てに、帰ってくるのは
...what comes back in the end is...
救われなかった君の声
...your voice that was not saved.
愛しい妹よ
My beloved sister...
そこに居たら教えて
If you are there, tell me...
君の手をいつかまた
Will I be able to hold your hand...
握れるのかな
...again someday?
Hello everyone! I hope you guys enjoyed the live.
And now that the live is over, I got some announcements for you guys. Wow!
Well first of all, it is the merch announcement. Woo!
This time around, I'm gonna be doing a Re-Released Edition Fashion Special. Wow!
You see some familiar and most requested items you guys kind of told me about.
So we're going to be releasing the TAKOD.EX Hoodie Re-Released Edition...
...and "Not-A-Bad-End" T-Shirt Re-Released Edition, a matching T-shirt with Ina!
And of course, when you have clothes, you gotta have a nice way to wash those clothes...
...so I'm also gonna be releasing "They-said-I-could-become-anything" Tako Mesh Laundry Pouch Re-Released Edition. Wow!
So all of these items are re-released, which means that they're gonna have a different tag...
...from their original, you know, released versions.
And these items are just a reproduction of the premium talent merch released in the past...
...and will have the special 2024 re-released edition label as the proof.
And up next, we got LINE stamps!
This is an official stamp pack that's gonna be released right after this live, wow, this stream, yes. Soon, very soon.
And it's drawn by none other than yours truly, Ninomae Ina'nis.
Honestly, I've always wanted like an easy to use stamp pack and I use LINE a lot...
...so I thought, you know, I'll take this chance to draw a whole set myself.
I hope you guys like it and I guess if you use LINE a bit, I hope you guys check it out.
I think they turned out pretty good, so...
The link will be in the description below, up, above, below, below, yes, somewhere in the description, so make sure to check it out!
CAST: Ninomae Ina'nis, Mori Calliope, IRyS...
...不知火フレア, 宝鐘マリン, Gawr Gura, 桃鈴ねね, 雪花ラミィ
...Shiranui Flare, Houshou Marine, Gawr Gura, Momosuzu Nene, Yukihana Lamy
THUMBNAIL: Ninomae Ina'nis / LOGO: 瑞真えぬ
THUMBNAIL: Ninomae Ina'nis / LOGO: Enu Mizuma
CHOREOGRAPHY: ミユキニシジマ
CHOREOGRAPHY: Miyuki Nishijima
FILM PRODUCTION: Lyric motion とこう, BG Animation すめるめ, トライフロンティア合同会社
FILM PRODUCTION: Lyric motion - Tokou, BG Animation - Sumerrume, TRIFRONTIER LLC
MUSIC: KosK, symny, きゅん, クックルP, ジョウコウ...
MUSIC: KosK, symny, Kyun, Cookle P, Joukou...
...ふじそば, まっこ, マッチ, 犬絵, 山本こーすけ
...Fujisoba, Makko, Match, Inue, Kosuke Yamamoto
Vocal Mix: 寺尾修一郎 (Blue owl sound)
Vocal Mix: Shuichiro Terao (Blue owl sound)
FILMING & PLANNING: カバー株式会社 / SPECIAL THANKS: Takodachi
FILMING & PLANNING: Cover Corp. / SPECIAL THANKS: Takodachi
EXECUTIVE PRODUCTION: Ninomae Ina'nis
Thank you everyone for all your love and support!
A lot happened while trying to put together this live...
...so I'm really happy I can share this with everyone!
Biggest thank you to all the staff, creators, friends...
...and, of course, to you all who could make this happen!!
I poured my heart into this live so I hope you all enjoyed it!
Thank you, thank you and thank you always! - Ninomae Ina'nis
手鞠
TEMARI
Vocal & Illust: Ninomae Ina'nis / Music & Mix: schat / Lyrics & Movie: LUMINA